<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kelvin&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kelvin&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 14:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mantaining few snapshots</title>
      <link>https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/xx-fewsnaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 14:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/xx-fewsnaps/</guid>
      <description>While my friend Victor and I were writing Kindelia, he implemented a solution to maintain a set of snapshots of the network&amp;rsquo;s memory and challenged us to find an algorithm with the same properties, as — I believe — an attempt to validate his solution as he had never found a similar solution being described, much less named.
The problem A computationally-heavy transaction is applied to the current state to get the next state ( $ S_{t+1} = f(S_t, x_t) ) $ at each time interval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Musical Game</title>
      <link>https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/01-the-real-musical-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 14:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.steinerkelvin.dev/posts/01-the-real-musical-game/</guid>
      <description>As I understand, music is like language. You have this written notation that you can translate to sound with a device — vocal cords and musical instruments. Sound that your brain interprets as concepts in your mind.
Composers and writers are wizards that translate concepts in their minds to these concrete written runes that, once spoken, or played through magical instruments, convey meaning — notes and melodies. Music.
When I learned to play the keyboard, I could translate the written notation directly into the equivalent notes on the instrument and slowly learn to play a song by sheer repetition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
